{"data":[{"question":"That is Mary ___ over there.","a":"sitting","b":"to sit","c":"to be sat","d":"being sat","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A present participle attributes a quality of action to the noun, which is viewed as undertaking the action \n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle \n- The present is an 'active' participle and the past is a 'passive' participle.\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The police caught him ___ a car.","a":"to steal","b":"stealing","c":"stolen","d":"to be stolen","answer":"2","explain":"\n- A present participle attributes a quality of action to the noun, which is viewed as undertaking the action \n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle \n- The present is an 'active' participle and the past is a 'passive' participle.\" ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"These are the facts _________ by the committee.","a":"to gather","b":"gathering","c":"gathered","d":"being gathered","answer":"3","explain":"\n- A present participle attributes a quality of action to the noun, which is viewed as undertaking the action \n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle \n- The present is an 'active' participle and the past is a 'passive' participle.\" ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"They got their car ___ at the garage.","a":"to wash","b":"washing","c":"being washed","d":"washed","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A present participle attributes a quality of action to the noun, which is viewed as undertaking the action \n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle \n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I had my suit ___ yesterday.","a":"to press","b":"pressing","c":"press","d":"pressed","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A present participle attributes a quality of action to the noun, which is viewed as undertaking the action \n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle \n- The present is an 'active' participle and the past is a 'passive' participle.\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The language ___ in Canada is English.","a":"to speak","b":"speaking","c":"spoken","d":"speaks","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- A present participle attributes a quality of action to the noun, which is viewed as undertaking the action\n\n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle\n\n- The present is an 'active' participle and the past is a 'passive' participle.\"\n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I am sorry to have kept you ___ so long.","a":"to wait","b":"waiting","c":"be waiting","d":"be waited","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Structure: Keep somebody doing something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"She kept her eyes ___ all the time.","a":"to close","b":"closing","c":"close","d":"closed","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Structure: Keep something + Part Participle","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Can Mary make herself ___ in English?","a":"understood","b":"understand","c":"to understand","d":"understanding","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A present participle attributes a quality of action to the noun, which is viewed as undertaking the action \n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle \n- The present is an 'active' participle and the past is a 'passive' participle.\" ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"A noise that disturbs someone is a ___ noise.","a":"disturb","b":"disturbance","c":"disturbed","d":"disturbing","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A present participle attributes a quality of action to the noun, which is viewed as undertaking the action \n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle \n- The present is an 'active' participle and the past is a 'passive' participle.\" ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}